Alexander, Gabriel Additional Arbitration Files 5678
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Warren Consolidated School District and Warren Education Association, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  Salaries: Reductions for Absence; Extra Duties. Closed May 16, 1967.
- Washburn Wire company and United Steelworkers of America, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Wages: Incentive Compensation. Closed May 26, 1971.
- Washburn Wire Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Contracting Out. Closed April 19, 1971
- Westinghouse Electric Corporation Grievance 1665 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Cancelled.
- White Products Corporation and United Auto Workers Local 1002, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Reporting Pay: Conditions Beyond the Company's Control. Closed June 23, 1965
- Whitehead and Kales and United Steelworkers of America, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Discipline: Insubordination. Closed June 10, 1966
- Whitehead and Kales and United Steelworkers of America, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Vacations: Plant Closings. Closed April 23, 1970
- Westinghouse Electric Power Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 2150, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Promotions: Qualifications: Testing. Closed July 21, 1969
- Wisconsin Electric Power Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 2150, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Promotions: Qualifications, Prior Discipline. Closed July 21, 1969
- Wyandotte Chemicals Corporation and Allied and Technical Workers, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Fringe Benefits: Supplemental Compensation for Industrial Injuries: Effect of Reduction in Force. Closed February 16, 1971.
- Greyhound Lines Incorporated and Amalgamated Transit Unions, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Discharge. Closed August 11, 1976.
- Dayton Power and Light and Utility Workers Union of America, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Discipline: Assault on Watchman. Closed October 6, 1970
- City of Detroit (DPW) and American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Discipline: Assault on Supervisor. Closed October 20, 1971
- City of Detroit (DPW) and American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Discipline: Fighting; Use of Weapons. Closed September 24, 1971.
- City of Detroit (Police Department) and Police Officers Association of Michigan Grievance Number - Comm-15, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Closed January 13, 1970
- City of Detroit (Police Department) and Police Officers Association of Michigan, Grievance Number TSB-2, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Closed June 2, 1971
- City of Detroit and Police Officers Association of Michigan, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Wages: Premium Pay for Cancelled Leave Days. Closed August 16, 1971
- Detroit Free Press and Newspaper Drivers and Handlers Union Local 372, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Vacation Pro Rata Grievance. Closed May 19, 1969
- Detroit Free Press and Detroit Typographical Union Number 18, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Seniority: Priority Claims to "Situations": Directors of Work Arbitration: Status Quo Relief. Closed August 14, 1963.
- John Deere Planter Works and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Work Assignments: Jib and Fixture Building. Closed September 22, 1972.
- John Deere Ottumwa Works and United Auto Workers Local 74, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Discipline: Assaulting a Supervisor. Closed April 29, 1971.
- John Deere - East Moline Works and United Auto Workers Local 865, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Discipline: Unauthorized Possession of Company Property. Closed August 31, 1970
- John Deere - East Moline Works and United Auto Workers Local 865, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Seniority: Loss of; Three Day Absence; Satisfactory Reason. Closed August 31, 1970
- John Deere - Dubuque Works and United Auto Workers Local 1536, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  Overtime: Equalization; Extended Absence. Closed September 8, 1970.
- John Deere - Waterloo Works and United Auto Workers Local 838, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  Discipline: Unauthorized Possession of Company Property. Closed November 17, 1970.
- Deere and Company - Atlanta Parts Depot and United Auto Workers Local 472, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  Discipline: Repeated Misconduct, Loitering and Wasting Time. Closed December 14, 1970.
- Deere and Company (Industrial Equipment Works) and United Auto Workers Local Union 1536, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  Seniority: Loss of; Absence. Closed January 26, 1971
- Ford Motor Company and United Plant Guard Workers of America Local 225, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  Recognition: Performance of Security Checking. Closed September 8, 1964
- Oakland Press and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 372, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Circulation Department District. Closed February 24, 1975.
- New England Telephone and Telegraph Company and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Discharge: Discipline, False Time Reports. Closed May 23, 1977.
- Ohio Crankshaft Division - Park-Ohio Industries, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Layoffs: Advance Notice; Returns from Sick Leave. Closed October 5, 1976.
- Ohio Crankshaft Division Park - Ohio Industries and United Auto Workers Local 91, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Discipline: Absenteeism; Last Chance Status. Closed October 15, 1976
- Ohio Crankshaft Division Park - Ohio Industries and United Auto Workers Local 91, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Wages: Holiday Pay - Calculation; Cost of Living Adjustment. Closed October 5, 1976
- Ohio Crankshaft Division Park - Ohio Industries and United Auto Workers Local 91, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Wages: Average Earnings for Off-Station Assignments. Closed October 11, 1976.
- Ohio Crankshaft Division Park - Ohio Industries and United Auto Workers Local 91, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Seniority: Loss of; Failure to Report for Work after Notice, "Proper Case" Exceptions. Closed October 15, 1976.
- Northwestern Steel and Wire Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Contracting Out: Crankshaft Machining. Closed August 29. 1974.
- Pontiac, City of and American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees Local 2002, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  Seniority: Layoffs. Closed February 23, 1973
- Pontiac, city of and Police Officers Association, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Conditions of Employment: Use of City Vehicles. Closed January 13, 1975
- Reserve Mining Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Wages: Classification; Grinding Mill Helper. Closed November 10, 1967
- Reserve Mining Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  Classification: Furnace Operator. Closed January 29, 1968.
- Reserve Mining Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Wages: Classification; Grinding Mill Operators. Closed November 10, 1967
- Reserve Mining Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Classification: Changed Job; Filter Finisher Operator. Closed December 6, 1967
- Greyhound Lines, Incorporated and Amalgamated Transit Union Division 1098, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Discipline: Fighting. Closed February 23, 1977
- Greyhound Lines, Incorporated and Amalgamated Transit Union Division 1313, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Discipline: Possession of Intoxicating Liquor. Closed May 5, 1978.
- Greyhound Lines, Incorporated and Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 1042, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Suspension: Discipline; At Fault Accident. Closed May 6, 1977
- Greyhound Lines, Incorporated and Amalgamated Transit Union Division 1126, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Discipline: Possession of Intoxicants; Seniority: Loss of; Quitting; Undue Influence. Closed August 15, 1977.
- Greyhound Lines, Incorporated and the Amalgamated Transit Union Division 1126, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Discharge: Procedure; Notice of Infraction. Closed August 17, 1977.
- Greyhound Lines, Incorporated and Amalgamated Transit Union, Division, Council of Greyhound Divisions, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Waiting Time Pay on Charter Drop- offs. Closed September 26, 1977.
- Greyhound Lines, Incorporated and United Auto Workers Local 985, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Fringe Benefits: Employee Parking Rates. Closed December 12, 1977
- Greyhound Lines, Incorporated and Amalgamated Transit Union Division 1042, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Discipline: Union-Company Understanding as to No Smoking Announcements. Closed March 7, 1978
- Greyhound Lines, Incorporated and Amalgamated Transit Union Division 1326, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Discipline: Failure to make Smoking Announcement; Second Offence, Inadvertence. Closed September 8, 1978.
- Greyhound Lines, Incorporated and Amalgamated Transit Union Division 1303, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  Discipline: At Fault Accident. Closed September 8, 1978.
- Greyhound Lines, Incorporated and Amalgamated Transit Union Division 1313, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Discipline: Negligence; Restitution by Employee. Closed September 22, 1978
- Northern Tube (United Auto Workers), Grievance 9619, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Working Hours: Short Work Weeks or Layoffs. Closed May 10, 1978.
- Pauly Cheese Company (Swift) International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 75, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Suspension. Closed October 27, 1976.
- Pennwalt Corporation and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Discipline: Fighting; Weapon. October 26, 1977.
- Pennwalt Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Fringe Benefits: Protective Clothing Issues. Closed March 26, 1979
- Reserve Mining Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 4757, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Local Working Conditions: Scheduling Helpers. Closed January 17, 1977
- Reserve Mining Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 5296, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Seniority: Reduction in Force; Reassignment of Work. Closed January 17, 1977.
- Saint John Hospital and International Union of Operating Engineers, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  Promotions: Ability, Journeyman Painter. Closed July 27, 1978.
- Saint Louis Post Dispatch and Saint Louis Mailers Union, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  Wages: Interim Pay Provision. Closed January 31, 1979.
- Vickers Incorporated and International Union of Electrical Workers Local 945, American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  Recognition: Bargaining Unit Work; Building Test Stands. Closed December 21, 1979.
- United States Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Local 5000, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  Seniority: Filling Vacancies During Extended Season. Closed September 18, 1978.
- Westinghouse Electric Company and International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  Seniority: Loss of. Closed October 18, 1978
- Wheeler Van Label Company and Grand Rapids Printing, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  Discharge: Work Stoppage; Leadership; Unfair Labor Practice Strike. Closed September 5, 1978
- Wheatland Tube Company and United Steelworkers of America Local Number 1660, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  Discipline: Careless Crane Operation. Closed October 16, 1979
- Willow Run Rubber and Lining Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 15407, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  Seniority: Loss of: Failure to Report Absence. Closed February 16, 1977.
- WKMF Incorporated and National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians Local 46, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  Discipline: Insubordination. Closed March 20, 1974.
- WOTV Incorporated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  Settled prior to hearing. No date.
- American Chain and Cable Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Equalization of Overtime. Closed April 11, 1979.
- Ames Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Recognition: Supervisor Performing Bargaining Unit Work. Closed November 14, 1979.
- Ames Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Recognition: Supervisor Performing Bargaining Unit Work. Closed November 14, 1979
- Akiva Hebrew Day School and Akiva Teachers Association, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Discharge. Closed June 5, 1979
- Borg-Warner Corporation and United Auto Workers, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Discipline: Chronic Absenteeism. Closed March 23, 1979.
- Cadmet Corporation and United Auto Workers Local 417, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Arbitrability: Time Limits for Filing Grievances. Closed July 5, 1979
- Diecast Corporation and United Auto Workers, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Discharge: Slowdown. Closed February 12, 1979.
- Dundee Cement Company and United Cement, Lime, Gypsum, and Allied Workers Local 408, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  Subcontracting: Major Modifications. Closed February 1, 1979
- Hastings Manufacturing Company and United Auto Workers Local 138, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  Bargaining Unit: Erosion: Performance of Clerical Work by Excluded Employees. Closed April 10, 1979
- Illinois Bell Telephone Company and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Locals 165 and 399, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  Snowstorm Grievances. Closed June 13, 1979.
- Inmont Corporation and United Auto Workers Local 492, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  Discipline: Careless Destruction of Company Property. Closed May 30, 1979.
- Lansing Mile District Sealtest Foods Division of Kraft, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  Wages: Guaranteed Pay; Snowstorm. Closed July 26, 1979.
- Lake Shore, Incorporated and United Steelworkers of America Local Unions 3111 and 3168, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  Wages: Classification Changed Job, Assembler. Closed May 2, 1978.
- Martin Marietta Aluminum of Kentucky Incorporated and United Steelworkers of America, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  Wages: Job Classification Procedure Wording of Job Descriptions. Closed May 24, 1977.
- Mountain State Steel Foundries and United Steelworkers of America, American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations Local 2294, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  Seniority: Reduction in Force; Bumping. Closed May 15, 1978.
- New England Telephone Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 2322, Case Number 1130-1168-76, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  Closed April 3, 1978
- New Jersey Bell Telephone Company and Transport Workers Union of New Jersey Local 827, Case Number 1330-1774-76, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  Suspension. Closed September 9, 1977.
- Western Greyhound Lines and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Discipline: Drinking While in Uniform. Closed December 15, 1969
- Eastern Greyhound Lines and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Blablock Discharge. Closed July 17, 1964.
- Eastern Greyhound Lines and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  LaRusso Discharge. Closed July 1, 1964
- Southern Greyhound Lines and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Discipline: Smoking. Closed December 2, 1969
- Greyhound Lines East and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Discipline. Closed July 13, 1973
- Greyhound Lines Incorporated and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Discharge. Closed April 14, 1976.
- Greyhound Lines East and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Atlanta Dormitory Cases. Closed October 27, 1972.
- Greyhound Lines East and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  Discharge. Closed April 21, 1972.
- Greyhound Lines East and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  Seniority: Loss of: Failure to Report During Absence. Closed July 22, 1975
- Greyhound Lines Incorporated (Memphis) and Amalgamated Transit Union Division 1323, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Discharge: Discipline: Loitering; Misappropriation of Property; Irregular Baggage Handling. Closed October 13, 1975
- Greyhound Lines and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Wage Rates: Part-Time Employees. Closed July 8, 1977.
- General Motors (Inland Division) and Local Number 87 - United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, Plastic Workers of America Case I-15, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  Closed October 3, 1962.
- General Motors (Dayton) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, Plastic Workers of America Case J-2, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  Closed October 3, 1962
- General Motors (Inland) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, Plastic Workers of America Local 87, Case I-16, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  Closed October 11, 1962
- General Motors (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, Plastic Workers of America, Case J-3, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- General Motors (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, Plastic Workers of America, Case J-4, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- General Motors (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, Plastic Workers of America, Case J-5, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  Closed April 1, 1963
- General Motors Corporation and Pattern Makers League of North America, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Recognition: Included Work, Plastic Checking Fixtures. Closed January 10, 1970
- General Motors Corporation and Pattern Makers League of North America, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Recognition: Included Work, Plastic Checking Fixtures. Closed January 19, 1970
- General Motors Corporation and Pattern Makers League of North America (Tech Center, Warren, Michigan), 1969 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Overtime Distribution: Part Time Employees. Closed January 24, 1969
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Manufacturing) and United Plant Guard Workers of America Local 166, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Discipline: Rule 33; Intoxicants. Unadjusted Complaint. Closed August 19, 1970.
- General Motors Corporation (Buick Retail Store) and United Auto Workers, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Representation: Pay for Committeeman Attending Meetings. Closed August 28, 1969.
- General Motors (Chevrolet Division) and United Plant Guard Workers of America, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Discipline: Inattention to Duty. Closed October 15, 1971.
- General Motors (Fisher Body Division) and United Auto Workers appeal Case Number 610, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Closed March 10, 1970
- Greyhound Lines East (Amalgamated Transit Union), 1970 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Discharge. Closed August 5 1970
- Greyhound Lines East - Amalgamated Transit union, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Discharge: At Fault Accident. Closed November 14, 1973.
- Greyhound Lines East - Amalgamated Transit Union, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Discharge: Discipline; Improper Driving; At Fault Accident. Closed January 29, 1974.
- Greyhound Lines East and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  Discipline: Disloyalty; Informing Authorities. Closed September 24, 1976
- Greyhound Lines East and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  Discipline: Misconduct away from work. Closed May 19, 1975.
- Greyhound Lines Incorporated and Amalgamated Transit Union (American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  Management's Rights: Disciplinary Policies; Unilateral Change in Penalty Scheme. Closed June 22, 1976.
- Central Greyhound Lines and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  Discharge. Closed February 24, 1969
- Eastern Greyhound Lines and Amalgamated Transit Union, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  Safe Driving: Right Turns. Closed September 5, 1968.
- Globe-Union Incorporated and International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers Local 1116, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Discipline: Arbitrability; Last Chance Agreement. Closed September 1, 1976
- Great Lakes Steel National Steel Corporation and United Plant Guard Workers of America, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  Discipline: Refusal to Shave Beard. Closed May 7, 1975.
- Great Lakes Steel and United Plant Guard Workers of America, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Discipline: Insubordination. Closed March 23, 1977.
- Hanna Furnace Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Local 2497, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Wages: Job Classification; Change in Job Content. Closed March 21, 1977
- Illinois Bell Telephone Company and System Council International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Recognition and Bargaining: Work Assignments to Excluded Employees. Closed December 12, 1978.
- United States Department of Treasury - Internal Revenue Service and National Treasury Employees Chapter Number 24, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  Fringe Benefits: Administrative Leave; Absence Caused by Inclement Weather. Closed July 13, 1976.
- Internal Revenue Service and National Treasury Employees, FCMS Case Number 74K/09563, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Closed October 30, 1974
- Hardy Salt Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Discipline: Leaving Work Station. Closed October 11, 1977.
- Hydride Packing Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 26, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  Discipline: Falsification on Employment Record. Closed November 1, 1977.
- Joliet (Illinois) Mass Transit District and Division 228, Amalgamated Transit Union, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  Contract Terms: General Wage Increase; Bereavement Clause. Closed July 6, 1978
- Kelsey-Hayes Company and Allied Industrial Workers Local 670, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  SUB Arbitration. Closed December 5, 1978
- Kennametal Incorporated and United Auto Workers of America Local 985, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  Discipline: Discharge for Absences. Closed June 15, 1977
- Lake Shore, Incorporated and United Steelworkers of America Local Unions 3111 and 3168, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  Assembler Classification. Closed June 1, 1977.
- Kellogg Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  Management's Rights; True Collective Bargaining, Contracting Out. Closed October 10, 1977.
- Michigan Seamless Tube Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 1900, Grievance 76110, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  Wages: Rate for Maintenance and clean-up During Vacation Shutdowns. Closed June 7, 1977.
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Case J-33, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Closed January 12, 1966
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Case K-6 through K-11, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Case K-21 through K-26, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Cases L-1 through L-5, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Cases L-6 through L-13, 1971-1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Case M-4, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  Discipline: Intoxication; Assaulting Supervisor. Closed February 28, 1973
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Case M-5, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  Working Hours; Scheduling Three Shift Operations. Closed March 28, 1973.
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Case M-28, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  Discipline: Assaulting Supervisor; Extent of Penalty. Closed September 9, 1974.
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  Discipline: Assaulting supervisor. Closed January 26, 1976
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  Discipline: Absent Without Cause; Medical Certifications. Closed May 25, 1976.